Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements, part 1, 1875-2001 and undated, bulk 1920s-1990s RL.00687
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Main Files Series, 1875-2001 and undated
  - Warner-Lambert, 1915-1997
    - 1960-1963 Listerine, 4 folders (Box WL14)
    - 1962-1971 Listerine, 7 folders (Box WL15)
      Includes African-American-oriented campaigns.
    - 1965-1973 Various products, 6 folders (Box WL16)
      Includes sweepstakes, youth- and African-American- oriented campaigns; Easprin Chewable Aspirin, Efferdent, Listerex Antibacterial Scrub, Listerine Breath Spray, Listerine Cold Tablets, Listerine Throat Lozenges, Listerol Disinfectant Spray.
    - 1971-1986 Various products, 6 folders (Box WL17)
      Includes Chewels, Efferdent, Entemann's, EPT, Listermint, Lubriderm, Personal Touch, Schick, Sinutab, Tempters, Throat Lozenges.
    - 1987-1997 Listerine and miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box WL18)
      Includes media schedule, bar graph 1925-1962, television show reviews, labels.
  - Wedgewood, 1974-1986
    - 1974-1983, 1985-1986 (Box WD1)
  - W.F. Young, 1937-1984
    Includes Absorbine For Horses and Absorbine Jr.
    - 1937-1939 (Box WF1)
    - 1940-1942 (Box WF2)
    - 1943-1945 (Box WF3)
    - 1946-1948 (Box WF4)
    - 1949-1957 (Box WF5)
    - 1959-1971 (Box WF6)
    - 1972-1984 (Box WF7)
  - Williams, J.B.: see J.B. Williams (Box WF7)
  - WXYZ--Channel 7 (Detroit), 1975-1982
    See also Channel 7 Action News in Oversice Box OV3.
    - 1975-1982 (Box WX1)
  - Young, W.F.: see W.F. Young (Box WX1)
- Small Files Series, 1901-1997 and undated
  Files for which only a small quantity (usually only one folder) of proofs or tearsheets has survived in the collection, mainly from the 1960s and later. A few clients are represented only by photocopies or prints made from microfilm, a fact which is noted in the list. The files are arranged alphabetically by client (not product) insofar as it has been possible to determine the client name accurately. Parenthetical information about the client, product, or the JWT office or division responsible for the ad has been added as appropriate. These clients are NOT represented in the Main Files Series but MAY have advertisements in the Oversize Series.
  - A Small Files, 1910s-1997
    - ACEMESA spanish olives (Chicago), 1985-1989 (Box AA1)
    - Activision (San Francisco), 1982-1983 (Box AA1)
    - Adolph Coors Co. (Chicago), 1984 (Box AA1)
    - AFSCME (American Federation of State and County Municipal Employees), 1983 (Box AA1)
    - Akzo Salt Inc., 1989-1995 (Box AA1)
    - Alexander Smith carpets, 1953-1959 (Box AA1)
    - Almaden Vineyards (San Francisco), 1969 (Box AA1)
    - Altec Lansing (San Francisco), 1969 (Box AA1)
    - AMAX (Brouillard), 1989 (Box AA1)
    - Ambiente! Pizza (Chicago), 1987 (Box AA1)
    - Amerada Hess, 1975-1977 (Box AA1)
    - American Cruises (San Francisco), 1988-1994 (Box AA2)
    - American Electric Power System, 1964-1966 (Box AA2)
    - American Gas and Electric Co., 1956-1957 (Box AA2)
    - American Greetings, 1986-1989 (Box AA2)
    - American Legal Systems (Brouillard), 1987 (Box AA2)
    - American Machine Foundry Co. bowling balls, 1966-1969 (Box AA2)
    - American Mechanical Toy Co., 1916 (Box AA2)
    - American Petroleum Institute, 1964, 1968-1969 (Box AA2)
      [See also Oversize Box OV1, Oversize Folder 3.]
    - American Physical Therapy Association, 1996-1997 (Box AA2)
    - American Postal Workers Union, 1983-1984 (Box AA3)
    - American Re, 1997 (Box AA3)
    - American Renolit Corp., 1965 (Box AA3)
    - American Sheep Producers Council, 1958-1960 (Box AA3)
    - America's Chemical Industry (Brouillard), 1980-1982 (Box AA3)
    - America's Credit Unions, 1981 (Box AA3)
    - ANCO (Anderson Co.) windshield wipers, 1979-1984 (Box AA3)
    - Anthracite Institute (hard coal for home heating), 1948-1951 (Box AA3)
    - A.P.S. Auto Parts (Detroit), 1983 (Box AA3)
    - Aquascutum raincoats, 1956-1957 (Box AA3)
    - Arbuckle Brothers (Yuban coffee), ca. 1910s (Box AA3)
    - Archdiocese of Detroit, 1976 (Box AA3)
    - Arrowhead Puritas water: see Beatrice Foods (Box AA3)
    - Arthur Anderson, 1991 (Box AA3)
    - ASOLIVA olive oil from Spain (Chicago), 1987-1988 (Box AA3)
    - Aspen Systems Corporation, 1969 (Box AA3)
    - Association of Casualty and Surety Companies, 1954 (Box AA3)
    - Atlantic Mutual (Brouillard), 1986-1991 (Box AA3)
    - Aurea jewelry (Brouillard), 1982-1983 (Box AA3)
    - Avail banking, 1984 (Box AA3)
  - B Small Files, 1939-1997
    - Ballantine Ale, 1939, 1947-1955 (Box BB1)
    - Bandai, 1996-1997 (Box BB1)
    - Banquet Foods (Chicago), 1974-1977 (Box BB1)
    - Baskin-Robbins (Los Angeles), 1985, 1987-1988 (Box BB1)
    - Bass (LGFE), 1982 (Box BB1)
    - Bay Area Cellular Telephone Co. (San Francisco), 1988 (Box BB1)
    - Beech-Nut, ca. 1968, 1969-1970 (Box BB1)
    - Bell Atlantic, 1989-1995 (Box BB1)
    - Bell--Northern Research (JWT recruitment), 1985 (Box BB1)
    - BellSouth Mobility (Atlanta), 1985-1988 (Box BB1)
      [See also Oversize Box OV2; Oversize Folder 6.]
    - Bendix, 1982 (Box BB1)
    - Bertoli USA olive oil, 1988 (Box BB2)
    - Better Homes and Gardens (Chicago), 1970 (Box BB2)
    - B.F. Goodrich Footwear--Long Lance shoe, approximately 1930 (Box BB2)
    - Big Sky of Montana, Inc. skiing, 1974 (Box BB2)
    - BioRics haircare, 1984 (Box BB2)
    - Boehringer and Ingleheim Pharmaceutical, 1974-1975 (Box BB2)
    - Booth's Distillery, 1976-1977 (Box BB2)
    - Bosch Corp.: see Robert Bosch (Box BB2)
    - Boyle-Midway (Sani-Flush), 1958-1960 (Box BB2)
    - Brand Names Foundation, 1964 (Box BB2)
    - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co., 1951-1955, 1969, 1990-1996 (Box BB2)
      [See also Oversize Folder 56.]
    - Brookfield Zoo (Chicago), 1989-1991, 1992-1993 (Box BB2)
    - Brown and Williamson cigarettes, 1977 (Box BB2)
    - Bryant, Lane: see Lany Bryant (Box BB2)
    - Buhl Realty Co. (Detroit), 1971-1973 (Box BB2)
    - Business Council of Georgia, 1990 (Box BB2)
  - C Small Files, 1904-1997
    - California Arts Council (San Francisco), 1989 (Box CC1)
    - California Beef Council (San Francisco), 1969 (Box CC1)
    - California Film Commission, 1994 (Box CC1)
    - California Raisin Advisory Board (San Francisco), 1969 (Box CC1)
    - California State Lottery, 1994-1996 (Box CC1)
    - California Tourism, 1994-1996 (Box CC1)
    - Capital Preservation Fund, 1982 (Box CC1)
    - Capitol Magnetic Products, 1974 (Box CC1)
      [See also Oversize Folder 8.]
    - Car Care Council (Detroit), 1969-1978, 1982-1984 (Box CC1)
    - Car X, 1988, 1992 (Box CC1)
    - Carey-Mcfall (Bali blinds), 1989 (Box CC1)
    - Carhartt outerwear (Detroit), 1983-1991 (Box CC1)
      [See also Oversize Box OV2; Oversize Folder 9.]
    - Carte Blanche (Los Angeles), 1969 (Box CC1)
    - Carter's ink, 1948 (Box CC1)
    - Cash Stream, 1984 (Box CC1)
    - Castle and Cook, Inc. (Bumble Bee, Dole), 1982, 1984, 1986 (Box CC1)
    - Cellular One mobile phones (San Francisco), 1989 (Box CC1)
    - Charles Williamson Stores (from microfilm), 1914 (Box CC2)
    - Chatham Complete Food Centers, 1976-1977 (Box CC2)
    - Chatham Manufacturing Co., ca. 1933 (Box CC2)
    - Cheek-Neal Coffee Company (Maxwell House), 1927-1928, 1930 (Box CC2)
    - Chevron (San Francisco), 1982-1984, 1988-1996 (Box CC2)
      Includes public service television programming, Ortho.
    - Chicago Board of Trade (Chicago), 1975 (Box CC2)
    - Chicago Economic Development Commission (Chicago), 1977-1979 (Box CC2)
    - Chip Soft, Inc., 1990-1991 (Box CC3)
    - Christian Dior, 1982-1984 (Box CC3)
      [See also Oversize Box OV3; Oversize Folder 13.]
    - Church and Dwight, 1951-1956 (Box CC3)
      Includes Arm and Hammer, Cow brands.
    - Ciba Pharmaceutical Products, 1956 (Box CC3)
    - CIGNA Healthplans of CA, 1992 (Box CC3)
    - Circle Line, 1981, 1986 (Box CC3)
    - CITCO (Brouillard), 1997 (Box CC3)
    - Citibank, 1991, 1993-1995 (Box CC3)
    - Citicorp Homeowners Inc., 1980 (Box CC3)
    - Cities Service Co. (energy and chemicals, 1978-1979 (Box CC3)
    - Citizens and Southern Banks in Georgia, 1972 (Box CC3)
    - Clairol, 1992-1997 (Box CC4)
    - Clear Start, 1995 (Box CC4)
    - Coast Fishing Co. (Los Angeles), 1930s (Box CC4)
      Includes Puss 'n' Boots cat food, Balto dog food.
    - Coldwell Banker Commercial Group (Los Angeles), 1988 (Box CC4)
    - Colt Industries (Detroit), 1981-1984 (Box CC4)
      Includes Holley automotive replacement parts.
    - Columbia Gas System, 1978 (Box CC4)
    - Columbia Mills, Inc., 1953, 1955 (Box CC4)
    - Computer Associates Software, 1989-1990 (Box CC4)
    - Computerland, 1983-1984 (Box CC4)
    - Condomania, 1990 (Box CC4)
    - Conductron Corp. Railroad (Los Angeles), 1969 (Box CC4)
    - Connecticut Mutual Alliance (Brouillard), 1989 (Box CC4)
    - Conroy's Florist (Los Angeles), 1987-1989 (Box CC4)
    - CONTEL (LGFE), 1982 (Box CC4)
    - Continental Motors, ca. 1916 (Box CC4)
    - Coors: see Adolph Coors Co. (Box CC4)
    - Corning Glass, 1918 (Box CC4)
    - Country Living, 1983 (Box CC4)
    - Craig, Jenny: see Jenny Craig International Weight Loss Centres (Box CC4)
    - Cream of Wheat, 1904-1905, 1925, 1927, 1930, 1933 (Box CC4)
    - Credit Union (Chicago), 1955-1956 (Box CC4)
    - Crisco: see Procter and Gamble (Box CC4)
    - Crosley Radio Corp., 1929 (Box CC4)
    - Cutter Biological, 1991 (Box CC4)
  - D Small Files, 1928-1997
    - Daewoo International Corp., 1983-1985 (Box DD1)
    - Davey Tree Expert Co., 1928 (Box DD1)
    - Dean Witter and Co. (San Francisco), 1968, 1970 (Box DD1)
    - DeBeers, 1996-1997 (Box DD1)
    - Del Taco / Naugles (Los Angeles), 1989 (Box DD1)
    - Del Webb, 1986-1988 (Box DD1)
    - Delta Dental Plan of Michigan (Detroit), 1992-1996 (Box DD1)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts (Detroit), ca. 1970, 1974, 1976 (Box DD1)
    - Detroit Renaissance Events, Inc. (Detroit), 1984 (Box DD1)
      Includes Detroit Grand Prix 3.
      [See also Oversize Folder 13.]
    - Deutsch Company Electronic Components Division, 1981 (Box DD1)
    - DeVilbiss (Detroit), 1976-1979 (Box DD1)
    - DeVoe and Reynolds Paint Store, 1957 (Box DD1)
    - Digital Communications Associates (Atlanta), 1987 (Box DD1)
    - Diners/Fugazy (Detroit), 1974 (Box DD1)
    - Dista Products Company (pharmaceuticals), 1982-1984 (Box DD1)
    - Dow Jones, 1996 (Box DD1)
      [See also Wall Street Journal, Oversize Box OV3.]
    - Dunlop golf balls, 1982-1984 (Box DD1)
    - Dunn and Bradstreet software, 1995 (Box DD1)
    - DuPont, Francis: see Francis DuPont (Box DD1)
    - DuroTest, 1981 (Box DD1)
  - E Small Files, 1943-1997
    - E.F. Hutton and Company, 1956 (Box EE1)
    - Emery Worldwide, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box EE1)
    - Empire City Savings Bank, 1955 (Box EE1)
    - Entergy, 1997 (Box EE1)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the U.S., 1943-1944 (Box EE1)
    - Esselete Pendaflex Corp., 1981-1984 (Box EE1)
    - European-American Bank and Trust Co., 1974-1977 (Box EE1)
    - Evans Products (Detroit), 1962 (Box EE1)
    - Executive Service Corps of Chicago (Chicago), 1989-1990 (Box EE1)
    - Eyelab, 1989 (Box EE1)
  - F Small Files, 1956-1997
    - Farrell Steamship Lines, 1956 (Box FF1)
    - Federal Express, 1991 (Box FF1)
    - Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corp., 1983-1992 (Box FF1)
    - Ferry-Morse Seed, 1968-1970 (Box FF1)
    - Financial Federation Inc., 1974 (Box FF1)
    - Financial Security Assurance (Brouillard), 1986-1990, 1992 (Box FF1)
    - Fine Arts Museum of San Francisco, 1988-1989 (Box FF1)
    - Firestone Tire Co., 1969-1971 (Box FF1)
    - First of Michigan Investments (Detroit), 1987 (Box FF2)
    - Fisher Price, 1986-1989 (Box FF2)
    - Flexco, 1986 (Box FF2)
    - Florsheim Shoes, 1994 (Box FF2)
    - Font Company, 1991 (Box FF2)
    - Foundation for Commercial Banks, 1958-1961 (Box FF2)
    - Fox Kids Network, 1997 (Box FF2)
    - Fram Corp. (Detroit), 1956-1972 (Box FF2)
    - Francis DuPont, 1956-1957, 1960-1962, 1964, 1983, 1985 (Box FF2)
    - Frankfort Distillers, 1967-1970, 1972 (Box FF2)
    - Franklin State Bank, 1974 (Box FF2)
    - Fred Joaillier, 1981-1984 (Box FF2)
    - Freddie-Mac, 1989-1991, 1992-1994 (Box FF2)
    - FTD, 1994 (Box FF2)
  - G Small Files, 1920s-1996
    - General Cigar (White Owl), ca. 1930s, 1940, ca. 1942, ca. 1950s (Box GG1)
    - General Motors International, 1920s-1930s (from microfilm), 1934 (Chevrolet) (Box GG1)
    - Genesco (Johnson and Murphy shoes), 1981-1983 (Box GG1)
    - Georgia Department of Tourism, 1993-1996 (Box GG1)
    - Georgia Federal Savings Bank (Atlanta), 1987-1993 (Box GG1)
    - Gift America, 1973-1974 (Box GG1)
    - Glasco Products Co., 1953 (Box GG1)
    - Godfather's Pizza (Chicago), 1986-1987 (Box GG1)
    - Good Humor, 1964-1966 (Box GG1)
    - Gorton, 1966-1968 (Box GG1)
    - Government Development Bank for Puerto Rico, 1978 (Box GG1)
    - Grace, W.R.: see W.R. Grace (Box GG1)
    - Grand Central, 1978 (Box GG1)
    - Grand Rapids Press (Detroit), 1976 (Box GG1)
    - Green Point Bank (Brouillard), 1995-1996 (Box GG1)
    - Gruen Watch Makers Guild, 1924, 1927, 1931 (Box GG1)
    - Guerlain, Inc., 1986-1993 (Box GG1)
  - H Small Files, 1956-1997
    - Hammond Organ Co. (Chicago), 1970 (Box HH1)
    - Harbortown Development Partnership (Detroit), 1989 (Box HH1)
    - Harper Group, 1959 (Box HH1)
    - Harris Corporation (Brouillard), 1982-1983 (Box HH1)
    - Harrison Conference Centers, 1975 (Box HH1)
    - Hart, Shaffner and Marx (Chicago), 1970-1971 (Box HH1)
    - Hawaii Express, 1983-1984 (Box HH1)
    - Health Alliance Plan (Detroit), 1987-1989 (Box HH1)
    - Health Management Strategies, 1987 (Box HH1)
    - Hearst Corp., 1984 (Box HH1)
    - Heinz: see H.J. Heinz (Box HH1)
    - Helio Aircraft Corp., 1963-1966 (Box HH1)
    - Heritage Kitchen Specialty Foods (San Francisco), 1989 (Box HH1)
    - Hewlett-Packard, 1982-1984 (Box HH1)
    - H.F. Ritchie, 1956-1960 (Box HH1)
    - Hilton International (LGFE), 1982 (Box HH1)
    - Hi-Tech Sports (San Francisco), 1989 (Box HH1)
    - H.J. Heinz, 1995, 1997 (Box HH1)
    - Hoechst, 1975 (Box HH1)
    - Holiday Inn, 1972-1974, 1975 (Box HH1)
    - Hollywood Park Race Track (Los Angeles), 1987 (Box HH2)
    - Honeywell, 1996 (Box HH2)
    - HandR Block, 1980 (Box HH2)
    - Hutton, E.F.: see E.F. Hutton (Box HH2)
  - I Small Files, 1929-1988
    - Illinois Tourism, 2008-2009 (Box II1)
    - Industrial Alcohol Institute, 1929 (Box II1)
    - Instinet: see Reuters (Box II1)
    - Institute for Health Maintenance, 1983 (Box II1)
    - Integrated Resources (Brouillard), 1987-1988 (Box II1)
    - International Shrimp Council, 1968 (Box II1)
    - International Spike, Inc. (Jobe's), 1973, 1975-1982 (Box II1)
    - Isacomm, Inc., 1983 (Box II1)
  - J Small Files, 1914-1990s
    - Jantzen, 1968-1970 (Box JJ1)
    - J.C. Penney, 1930-1931 (from microfilm) (Box JJ1)
    - Jeffery, Thomas B.: see Thomas B. Jeffery (Box JJ1)
    - Jenny Craig International Weight Loss Centres, 1989-1994 (Box JJ1)
    - Jimsons Novelties and Gags, ca. 1990s (Box JJ1)
    - Joaillier, Fred: see Fred Joaillier (Box JJ1)
    - John Wanamaker, 1914 (from microfilm) (Box JJ1)
    - Johnson and Johnson, 1969, 1975 (Box JJ1)
    - JWP, Inc. (Brouillard), 1989-1990, 1992-1993 (Box JJ1)
  - K Small Files, 1956-1990
    - Kaiser Permanente (San Francisco), 1988-1990 (Box KK1)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1988-1989 (Box KK1)
    - Kidde, Inc., 1984 (Box KK1)
    - Kimberly-Clark (includes Depends), 1999-2009 (Box KK1)
    - King's Island, 1975-1976 (Box KK1)
    - Kingsberry Homes, 1956-1962 (Box KK1)
    - KNBC, 1969 (Box KK1)
    - Knomark, Inc. (Ty-D-Bol), 1983 (Box KK1)
    - Kulov Distributors, 1974 (Box KK1)
    - Kuppenheimer, 1984 (Box KK1)
  - L Small Files, 1917-1990s and undated
    - LA Cellular Telephone, 1988 (Box LL1)
    - Labbatt Brewery, 1971, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box LL1)
    - Lane Bryant, 1973 (Box LL1)
    - Le Marais, 1996 (Box LL1)
    - Lee Kum Kee, 2009 (Box LL1)
    - Les Halles, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box LL1)
    - Libby, McNeill and Libby (Chicago), 1917, 1919, 1933, 1947, 1963, 1970, 2 folders (Box LL1)
    - Liebmann Breweries (Rheingold beer), 1962-1963 (Box LL1)
    - Life of Virginia (LGFE), 1982 (Box LL1)
    - Loctite glue, 1982-1984 (Box LL1)
    - Log Cabin Products Company, 1922 (Box LL1)
    - Lone Star Industries, 1975-1977 (Box LL1)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Los Angeles), 1983, 1987-1990 (Box LL1)
    - Löwenbräu: see Miller Brewing Company in Main Files Series (Box LL1)
    - Lowe's, 1981-1985 (Box LL1)
    - Lynnwear Corp., 1980 (Box LL1)
    - Lyons Group, The, 1995 (Box LL1)
    - Lyons Restaurants (Chicago), 1995 (Box LL1)
  - M Small Files, 1960-1997
    - Magazine Publishers Association, 1966 (Box MM1)
    - Magic of Mark Wilson (JWT Entertainment Div.), ca. 1974 (Box MM1)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1987 (Box MM1)
    - Marathon Carey-McFall Co. (Bali blinds): see Carey-McFall Co. (Box MM1)
      [See also Oversize Folder 31.]
    - MCARE, 1995 (Box MM1)
    - McCoy Industries carpentry (Detroit), 1983 (Box MM1)
    - McCulloch Chain saws, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Box MM1)
    - Mead Johnson International and Domestic, 1960-1961, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box MM1)
    - Medalist Apparel, 1988 (Box MM1)
    - Mellon Bank Corp., 1982-1986 (Box MM1)
    - Mennen Company, 1967-1969 (Box MM1)
    - Merial Ltd. (IVOMEC), 1997 (Box MM1)
    - Merrill Lynch, 1963-1965 (Box MM1)
    - Michigan National Corporation Bank (Detroit), 1981-1984 (Box MM1)
    - MIDAS, 1996 (Box MM2)
    - Midcon, 1982-1983, 1992 (Box MM2)
    - Miles Laboratories, Inc., 1968-1978, 1982-1983, 1991, 1993 (Box MM2)
    - Milwaukee Road Railroad, 1961-1970, 1974 (Box MM2)
    - Mobil Oil, 1963 (Box MM2)
    - Mobilink, 1994 (Box MM2)
    - Monsanto textiles (Brouillard), 1974 (Box MM2)
    - Morgan Stanley, 1992-1997 (Box MM2)
    - Moseley insurance (Brouillard), 1985-1986 (Box MM2)
    - Motorola, 1990-1991, 1993-1997 (Box MM2)
    - MPAC Sports Day, 1991 (Box MM2)
    - Munsingwear, 1981-1982 (Box MM2)
      [See also Oversize Folder 35.]
    - Murine (Abbott Laboratories), 1963, 1965, 1970 (Box MM2)
  - N Small Files, 1901-1996
    - Nabisco Brands Inc. (Lamont Corliss Co.), 1982-1986, 1990-1993 (Box NN1)
    - National Airlines, 1979-1980 (Box NN1)
    - National Car Rental, 1963 (Box NN1)
    - National Fisheries Institute, 1965-1966 (Box NN1)
    - National Homes Corp., 1959 (Box NN1)
    - National Institute for Automotive Services Excellence (Detroit), 1983 (Box NN1)
    - National Phonograph Co., 1901 (Box NN1)
    - National Technical Systems, 1981 (Box NN1)
    - National Westminster Bank, 1970s (Box NN1)
    - Nestlé Company, 1981-1995, 2008 (Box NN1)
    - New Dick Van Dyke Show (JWT Entertainment Division), ca. 1975 (Box NN1)
    - New York Central System, 1954, 1956 (Box NN1)
    - New York City Opera, 1981 (Box NN1)
    - New York Clearing House, 1974 (Box NN1)
    - New York Jazz Museum, ca. 1974 (Box NN1)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange, 1990-1992, 1994-1995 (Box NN1)
    - New York Shipping Association, 1963 (Box NN2)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1990-1991 (Box NN2)
    - New York University, 1980s (Box NN2)
    - New York World Fair Corp., 1964-1965, international and domestic 1961-1964 (Box NN2)
      [See also Oversize Box OV24; Oversize Folder 36.]
    - Norfolk Southern Corp., 1982-1996 (Box NN2)
    - Northam Warren (Odorono), 1916-1939 (Box NN2)
    - Northern Pacific Railroad, 1927 (copies from microfilm) (Box NN2)
    - Northwest Airlines, 1991-1992 (Box NN2)
    - NYNEX (includes N.Y. Telephone), 1993, 1996 (Box NN2)
  - O Small Files, ca. 1932-1996
    - Odorono: see Northam Warren (Box OO1)
    - Old Jim Young's Apples, 1947-1950 (Box OO1)
    - Old Witch Co., ca. 1932 (Box OO1)
    - Olive Administration Committee (San Francisco), 1969 (Box OO1)
    - Olivetti, 1980-1982 (Box OO1)
    - Olympia, 1983-1984 (Box OO1)
    - Oneida Limited (Heirloom sterling), 1949, 1956-1960 (Box OO1)
    - Original Appalachian Artworks, 1984-1986 (Box OO1)
    - Outboard Marine Corp., 1995-1996 (Box OO1)
  - P Small Files, 1901-1997
    - Pabst Brewing Co., 1901 (Box PP1)
    - Pagenet, 1997 (Box PP1)
    - Pannell Kerr Forster, 1980 (Box PP1)
    - Paramount Home Video, 1987-1989 (Box PP1)
    - Parke-Davis, 1973 (Box PP1)
    - Payless Drugstores, 1993, 1995 (Box PP1)
    - Penick and Ford Ltd., Inc., 1930 (Box PP1)
    - Penn Central Corp. (Brouillard), 1982, 1984-1986 (Box PP1)
      Includes Marathon Le Tourneau; for Marathon Carey-McFall Co. (Bali blinds) see Carey McFall (Small Files Series)
    - Penney, J.C.: see J.C. Penney (Box PP1)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1926-1927, ca. 1930 (Box PP1)
    - Pepsi Co., 1964, 1979, 1987, 1992-1997 (Box PP1)
    - PGA Golf Championship, 61st (Detroit), 1978 (Box PP1)
    - Pharma-Craft Corp. deodorant, 1948, 1956 (Box PP1)
    - Philip Morris, 1964 (Box PP1)
    - Phoenix Hosiery, 1933 (Box PP1)
    - Phone-Mate, 1984-1988 (Box PP1)
    - Piggly Wiggly Stores, 1928 (Box PP1)
    - Pillsbury Co., 1994 (Box PP1)
    - Pineapple Grower's Association (San Francisco), 1969 (Box PP1)
    - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1962-1963 (Box PP1)
    - Platinum Jewelry, 1976-1977 (Box PP1)
    - Play Cable (Landsdowne), 1983 (Box PP2)
    - Plus Systems, Inc., 1988-1993, 1995-1996 (Box PP2)
    - Prebon Yamane, 1996-1997 (Box PP2)
    - Precision Tune, 1989 (Box PP2)
    - Premier Magazine, 1987 (Box PP2)
    - President's Council on Youth Opportunity: see Advertising Council (Main Files Series) (Box PP2)
    - Presto Foods, 1988-1989 (Box PP2)
    - Prince (Brouillard), 1991-1993 (Box PP2)
    - Princess Cruises, 1995-1997 (Box PP2)
    - Procter and Gamble (Crisco), 1912 (Box PP2)
    - Prodigy, 1988-1994 (Box PP2)
    - Pro-Phy-Lac-Tic Brush Co., 1963-1964, 1966-1968 (Box PP2)
    - Prudential Insurance Co., 1901, 1906 (Box PP2)
    - Publicker Distillers, 1974-1975 (Box PP2)
    - Putnam Funds, 1974-1975 (Box PP2)
    - Putnam Trust, 1963-1964 (Box PP2)
  - Q Small Files, 1966-1982
    - Quality Paperback Book Club, Inc. (LGFE), 1982 (Box QQ1)
    - Quality School Plan, 1966-1968 (Box QQ1)
  - R Small Files, 1925-1997 and undated
    - Radio City Music Hall, Snow White, ca. 1979, ca. 1981 (Box RR1)
    - Ragu Foods Inc., 1983, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box RR1)
    - Real Silk, 1928, 1930 (Box RR1)
    - Really Rosie, 1981 (Box RR1)
    - Red Barn, 1971-1976 (Box RR1)
    - Renaissance Center (Detroit), 1983 (Box RR1)
    - Reuter (Brouillard), 1990 (TV 2000) and undated (INSTINET) (Box RR1)
    - Richardson Company, 1925 (Box RR1)
    - Ritchie, H.F.: see H.F. Ritchie (Box RR1)
    - R.J. Reynolds, 1968-1970, 1972, 1984 (Box RR1)
    - Robert Bosch (Detroit), 1988-1997 (Box RR1)
    - Ronkin Educational Group, 1991 (Box RR1)
    - Ronrico, 1968-1970, 1974 (Box RR1)
    - Rowntree DeMets, 1983-1987 (Box RR1)
    - Roxane Laboratories, 1990-1992 (Box RR1)
    - Ryder, 1983-1984 (Box RR1)
      [See also Oversize Box OV25; Oversize Folder 40.]
  - S Small Files, 1927-1990s
    - Saba Technologies, 1987 (Box SS1)
    - Safe Brands Co., 1985 (Box SS1)
    - St. Supery Vineyards and Winery, ca. 1990s (Box SS1)
    - Salvatore Ferragamo (Brouillard), 1983-1984 (Box SS1)
    - Sasson Jeans, Inc., 1984 (Box SS1)
    - Schieffelin and Co., Inc. (Hennessey cognac), 1985 (Box SS1)
    - Schuller, 1996 (Box SS1)
    - Scientific American (LGFE), 1982 (Box SS1)
    - Screenvision Cinemas, 1978, 1980 (Box SS1)
    - Scripto, 1962 (Box SS1)
    - Seagram Distillers Co., 1968-1970 (Box SS1)
    - Searle Laboratories, 1975-1977, 1978, 1982 (Box SS1)
    - Selchow and Righter, 1978-1982 (Box SS1)
    - Seth Thomas, 1951-1955 (Box SS1)
    - Sharp and Dohme Medical, 1933 (Box SS1)
    - Shedd's (Mario olives), 1984 (Box SS1)
    - Sherwin-Williams Co., 1991, 1996-1997 (Box SS1)